(Today's My Star and Seo Jin share a special connection.)
When did you meet him for the first time?
(When did you meet My Star for the first time?)
As far as I can remember, I was in my 20s.
How did you guys meet?
He's friends with everyone around me.
(A basketball legend...)
(who once dominated the court)
(Korea's national treasure of a center, Seo Jang Hoon)
(Seo Jin, who gave off the vibe of a manager who'd studied abroad)
He's around my age, and we grew up in the same era.
(They spent their youth together.)
I thought he was the funniest.
I said, "You're the funniest person I know."
And he was like, "Hey, you're the funniest to me."
I love him.
(My Star has been his beloved friend for 30 years.)
Is there anything about him that you're jealous of?
(Thinking)
- His wealth? - Wealth?
Who is richer?
I'm sure Jang Hoon is richer.
Have you even tried comparing?
There's no need. I surrender.
(A fortune so immense that even the Young Master bows out?)
Someone has a lump of gold.
That's Young Master.
Someone has ten lumps of gold.
That's My Lord.
(Lord Seo Jang Hoon)
He's the wealthiest person I've met.
My Lord.
Is it okay to spend over 10,000 dollars on a get-together?
Yes.
You can spend that much money?
With a net worth of two billion dollars,
even if you spend 100,000 dollars a day, you'd never run out of money.
Gosh, that's impossible.
Why did you put the building up for sale?
(Will he manage My Star's assets for the first time on the show?)
(A billionaire giant)
(But there's something he has more of than money.)
Why are you so mad?
It's because I'm mad.
(He has a short temper.)
I've never met anyone...
who complains as much as he does in my entire life.
He used to glare at people.
Foul!
(He shows explosive rage on "Divorce Camp.")
What are you doing?
(A man who's always angry whenever he's on TV)
(An angry giant)
(But there's one person who can match him)
You should teach Jang Hoon.
You didn't study much as a kid because you were playing sports.
He didn't have time to study because he was busy training.
Do you even know how to write your name in Chinese characters?
You've just crossed the line.
"Do you even know how to write your name in Chinese characters?"
(He's laughing so hard he's about to cry.)
That's ridiculous!
(Rage explosion)
It's funny.
I like when Jang Hoon reacts like that.
I love it when he gets mad.
(I'd love to see Seo Jin and Jang Hoon together.)
(They're both Thinkers.)
I'm a Thinker, but have a warm heart.
- Seo Jin is grumpy. - Yes.
(Cold Thinker Young Master...)
(versus Warm Thinker Lord)
(Who will win the Thinker battle between these friends of 30 years?)
(A makeup studio in Cheogdam-dong at 9am)
(He casually gets his makeup done while waiting for the secretaries.)
I might be running late at this rate.
(The secretaries are here.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Are you the manager?
I'm Ko Hag Yun. And I'm Jang Hoon's manager.
- Were you a basketball player too? - No.
- No? - No.
Were you a martial artist?
- No. - You look like an athlete.
- You were an athlete, right? - No.
No?
(I was scared for no reason.)
You know Jang Hoon is very meticulous about hygiene.
- Yes. - So...
- he... - Why are you shaking? Relax.
Don't be nervous.
(Come to think of it...)
(Shaking)
Why are you shaking? Relax.
(Licking)
(He doesn't know where to look.)
Why are you shaking? Relax.
- Does he punch you or something? - No.
Why are you shaking so much?
It's my first time on TV.
(My gosh)
Today, he's going to film...
his EBS show, "Seo Jang Hoon's Millionaire Next Door,"
which he hosts.
(The show he hosts...)
(travels across the country to meet millionaires...)
(and uncovers the secrets to their success.)
(His number one concern is revenue.)
(Daily revenue of 1.2 million dollars)
(Annual revenue up to 48 million dollars)
(Annual revenue of over 100 million dollars)
(Impressed)
(Evey week, he goes in search of people who are truly rich.)
Today, he's going to film his EBS show...
"Seo Jang Hoon's Millionaire Next Door," which he hosts.
The filming location is Gangneung.
(Gangneung?)
(Seoul, Gangneung)
(Today, they have to drive more than 3 hours each way.)
The second shoot will take place...
- I see. - at Haslla Art World,
which is run by a millionaire.
You know Jang Hoon is very meticulous about hygiene.
(I know it very well.)
It's an emergency whenever he needs to find a restroom.
You have to find a clean restroom.
Does he not use the restrooms at highway rest stops?
He doesn't really use them.
Then what kind of restrooms does he use on the highway?
He usually just holds it in.
- He holds it in? - He's that picky?
You know my personality.
- I see. - I see.
(Being a germaphobe,)
(his weakness is public restrooms.)
It's good to drink a lot of water.
He doesn't drink water because he doesn't want to use the restroom.
The restroom here is nice. Do you want to go?
- Maybe later. I'll think about it. - Okay.
(They might have to manager even his bodily functions.)
I'd appreciate it if you could find a clean restroom for him.
(I knew it.)
And he doesn't eat during a shoot.
- Does he eat nothing? All day? - He doesn't eat at all.
It's Jang Hoon.
(Glaring)
- Are they still not here? - They're talking.
(Are they still not here?)
(He's worried about being late for the shoot.)
They shouldn't take this long.
It takes 2 hours and 50 minutes to get there.
(Displeased)
Since he's tall,
be careful not to let his head get caught on the branches.
We can't even see them.
I always keep an eye on it.
(This is quite unusual.)
When he's feeling down,
show him cute videos or photos of puppies or babies.
Does he have a dog?
- You... - Babies?
- Does he like babies? - Yes.
- And... - He's crazy.
(Gasping)
(Is someone talking about me behind my back?)
I took a video of a baby a few days ago.
- You did? - I can show it to him.
I was at a housewarming party.
- What's this? - The bag you need on set.
Why are there so many things?
(A bag full of items for Giant)
(Heavy)
Why are there so many things?
(The bag is full of something.)
It's hand wash.
(Everyone pauses.)
(As expected, there's a hygiene item.)
(You can already guess what the rest of the items are.)
(They're finally going to meet My Star.)
Jang Hoon.
- Hello. - We might be running late.
There was so much traffic.
(These best friends haven't met for a while.)
- Hello. - Oh, my.
- It's cold. Take this. - What's this?
- This is what you're advertising. - Yes.
I was actually going to buy one.
Use these blankets to sit on or cover yourself with.
Thank you.
I see this brand's store every day...
on my commute,
so I thought I should buy one.
You can just tell me.
Thank you.
You can wash it with water,
so you can just throw it in the wash whenever you want.
You can wash it often.
I'm sure you'll wash it every day.
I wash my blankets every day, so this is nice.
Thank you.
Apparently, wool is good for men.
(My Star is happy with the gift.)
We have a long drive ahead of us, and you guys came.
- Of all days. - Right. Of all days.
Are you okay with driving?
Gangneung is far.
And it's raining too.
(The estimated driving time is 3 and a half hours.)
(And it's raining.)
- I know. - He won't say a thing...
while driving.
I feel nervous too.
His eyesight has gotten a lot worse lately.
(Aged eyes on top of wet roads)
You have trouble seeing small things and things up close.
(Spraying)
I have trouble seeing my phone screen.
(Looking intently)
Gosh. She's using a lot of hairspray.
- Are you jealous? - What?
- Are you jealous? - I am.
(My Star has hair that needs to be kept in place.)
- You should use some too. - No, I can't.
His hair doesn't look like it's going anywhere.
(Confirmed by a hair expert)
He has thick hair.
She used half a can of hairspray.
(Even after using half a can of hairspray,)
(his thick hair stays perfectly slicked back,)
(even in rain or snow.)
His hair is really thick.
(This is his signature hairstyle.)
She's been styling my hair...
this way...
for about 12 years.
She's the best in the country at this hairstyle.
(The ultimate slicked-back hair expert)
Because she does it...
every day.
I need...
to come here every day.
I can't get it done on set.
No one else can style my hair like this.
- It's neat. - My gosh.
You look sleek and neat.
- Let's go. - How about your clothes?
- I should get changed. - Here?
No.
- Thank you. Have a nice day. - Thank you.
- Jang Hoon, get in the car quickly. - Yes.
- Oh, my. - Please open the back door.
Sure.
- Welcome. - Oh, my.
My goodness.
Even when I sit in this car,
there's still plenty of room here.
- Isn't it cramped? - No, it's not.
It's a nice car.
The leather looks really nice too.
- Please close the door. - Okay.
(As always, he looks after My Star in his own nonchalant way.)
The window closes in such a cool way.
Try lowering the sunshade.
It'll come down from the top.
Lower it.
(He'll protect My Star's skin.)
And...
this seat has a massage function.
You can control everything with the remote.
That's nice.
(Turning on the massage function)
- Does it work? - Yes, it does.
(Smiling)
Let's get going.
Let me know if you need anything.
Thank you.
(To the studio in Gangneung for his first scheduled shoot)
It's an honor...
to ride in a car driven by Kwang Kyu.
- No, it's an honor for me... - No.
to drive for a billionaire like you.
"A billionaire?"
You're like My Lord.
(My Lord)
Have you eaten, My Star? Did you have breakfast?
I don't eat anything.
- Not before a shoot? - No.
When do you eat then?
I eat at home after everything is over.
- So do you eat once a day? - Yes.
You must be hungry.
I do a lot of shoots where I watch videos.
Right. Most of the time.
When I keep watching videos,
I get sleepy.
And I have to use the restroom.
You work so hard even if you have a lot of money.
Your net worth is in the hundreds of millions of dollars.
My net worth is what?
Hundreds of millions of dollars.
No, I don't have that much money.
By the way, why did you put the building up for sale?
There were articles about it.
- The building? - I want to buy it.
So how many buildings do you have?
- Sorry? - How many buildings do you have?
Two or three?
(He has 3 buildings.)
- I have three. - You do?
I want to buy it.
Go ahead.
You don't have money.
Everyone has their own struggles.
My gosh.
Hee Chul kept saying...
on "Men on a Mission..."
that I had hundreds of millions of dollars,
and eventually, he even claimed I had two billion dollars.
Right. Over a billion dollars.
So everyone thinks I have two billion dollars.
But do you know how many people in our country...
have a net worth of over two billion dollars?
Maybe 20 to 30 people?
I looked it up on the Internet.
Okay.
There are 35 people.
And you're one of them?
(Is he 1 of the 35 people?)
You're amazing.
- That means... - My Lord.
five or six out of a hundred people believe it.
They really believe it.
- Right. - I mean...
what could I possibly do...
(I'm not on the list of people worth 2 billion dollars.)
to make two billion dollars? That's what I ask.
How many people do you think in our country...
have a net worth of over 50 million dollars?
- Over 50 million dollars? - Yes.
About 500 people?
- There are about 5,000 people. - About 5,000 people?
- Yes. - And My Lord is one of them.
- Come on. - He is.
(Does he have a net worth of over 50 million dollars?)
- You're not one of them, Seo Jin. - No, I'm not.
Not even close.
- Unfortunately, - It's unfortunate.
Seo Jin...
- doesn't have 50 million dollars. - Not even close.
You must have over five million dollars, though.
But...
With a net worth of two billion dollars,
even if you spend 100,000 dollars a day, you'd never run out of money.
Right. He'll never run out.
- Did you say 100,000 dollars? - Yes.
- That's impossible. - Yes.
Apparently, it's hard to spend ten million dollars a year...
just on everyday living expenses, like food, shopping and drinks.
- It's impossible. - Right.
Even if you have a lot of money,
you wouldn't go to a fancy sushi restaurant every day.
- No, you wouldn't. - Right?
I want to eat gimbap and doenjang stew too.
Even if it's expensive...
(Even if you spend a lot, it's hard to spend 10 million dollars a year.)
- Even if you try hard... - Even if you buy expensive stuff...
It's not easy...
- to go shopping every day... - Or to buy luxury goods.
You could just buy your girlfriend a bag every day.
Still, it's not easy to do it...
- every day. - How can you go shopping every day?
How can you go to a department store every day?
I wish I had ten million dollars.
(The driver can't relate to it.)
How did you become so rich?
Gosh.
- How? - I'm not that rich.
I didn't spend the money I made...
as an athlete,
so I was able...
to keep saving it.
I saved the money I earned,
and over time,
it just kept growing.
- I think this is the key. - It's very important.
What do you spend most of your money on these days?
- Me? - I'm curious. Yes.
The only thing...
I spend money on for myself each month is...
(Does he buy a building?)
(Does he invest in stocks?)
food delivery.
That's the only thing.
(For a man worth 2 billion dollars, he lives a rather modest lifestyle.)
I don't buy anything.
I want to buy clothes,
but nothing fits.
(He saves money on everything except food.)
Do you try to save electricity at home too?
- I do. - You do?
Seo Jin is no joke.
I also save a lot.
I try to keep my expenses...
as low as possible.
That's the right thing.
That's a good habit.
I'm in good hands with two billionaires.
Oh, my.
Jang Hoon...
once treated me, Yu Hui Yeol, and Na Yeong Seok...
to a really nice meal.
(When My Star treats people, he goes all out.)
He treated us to a really nice meal.
Yeong Seok went to the same college as Jang Hoon.
- Oh, right. - He's two years younger than me,
and he was a year behind me in college.
He probably didn't even dare look at you back then.
- I didn't know him back then. - It was impossible.
He was a superstar at Yonsei University.
(He was a star basketball player at Yonsei University.)
- Right. - Back then, his basketball team...
was legendary.
(My Star, Jang Hoon, was a legend.)
(The youngest-ever MVP...)
(of the Korean Basketball Festival in 1993 and 1994)
(League leader in rebounds in his rookie season in 1998)
(A 2-time regular-season MVP)
(A 2-time championship winner)
(My Star was basketball itself.)
There was a rumor...
that whenever the Yonsei University basketball team...
went to a local bar,
they'd start off by drinking 40,000ml of beer per person.
Who does that?
It must be 4L.
No, I heard they drank 40L of beer.
The most beer I've ever seen anyone drink...
was 20 to 30L.
- That's a lot. - It's impossible. That's a lot.
- That's a lot of beer. - So...
Do you drink about 10L of beer?
No.
- Not anymore. - He can handle it.
I'm too old now.
Have you ever finished a whole bottle of liquor then?
A bottle? He drinks 2 to 3 bottles.
- He can drink 4 to 5L of liquor. - No.
(Jang Hoon can drink about 6 bottles of liquor.)
No.
No way. 4 to 5L of liquor?
He'll die.
- Liquor? - I used to drink with him a lot.
If you drink 4 to 5L of liquor, you'll die.
No. I'm sure you used to drink that much.
(- You'll die. - No, I saw you drinking that much.)
Alcohol?
I drank with him ten years ago.
There were other people too.
He drank three bottles.
Three bottles of liquor.
(He gets dizzy just by thinking about it.)
I suddenly blacked out.
- Really? - I don't remember anything.
I don't remember what happened after that.
(Even Seo Jin, who can usually hold his liquor, blacked out that day.)
So Jang Hoon can drink more than you.
Isn't it obvious?
Do you think I'd want to outdrink him?
(Jang Hoon is way ahead of him in both money and drinking.)
Has anyone ever asked you to commentate on a basketball game?
- They have. - Okay.
SBS recently asked me to do commentary...
- for the international games. - For Asia?
But I couldn't make it.
- Right. You're doing so many shows. - Yes.
And this is...
what I think.
Basketball isn't my profession anymore.
I don't want to offend the younger players...
or those who are still working in the sport.
So I try to stay away...
from basketball-related interviews and stuff.
You're smart indeed.
(My Star is wise.)
But since you have a connection to international games in Asia,
- Right. - I can see why they'd ask you.
Korea won the gold medal...
at the international event in Busan in 2002,
for the first time...
- in 20 years. - Right.
In 2002,
the Chinese team had Yao Ming.
When he was standing...
in front of me, I couldn't even see the rim.
He's 227cm tall.
He's tall.
(Yao Ming was an NBA superstar at the time.)
Every play starts with Yao Ming.
(He could dunk with just a little jump.)
(He was known as the "Walking Great Wall.")
He was tall even in the NBA.
- He was one of the tallest players. - He was one of the tallest players.
When he waved...
his arms around,
I couldn't even see the backboard.
Yao Ming was that tall?
You're lying.
- That's impossible. - Think about it.
You couldn't see the backboard?
He's 227cm,
and is right in front of you.
How tall are you?
I'm 205cm now.
He's 227cm tall, and when he raises his arms,
- He can touch the rim. - he reaches over 3m.
Then...
He could score without even jumping.
If he raised his arms in front of me,
I wouldn't be able to see a thing.
My gosh. I still don't understand how we could win.
How many points did you win by?
It was just unbelievable.
With a minute and a half left,
we were down by ten.
- And we... - You turned the tables?
We managed to tie it up, take it into overtime,
and win.
There's no way you can come back...
from a ten-point deficit with just a minute and a half left.
It's not easy.
(2002 men's basketball final at the international event)
(Their opponents were China, a basketball powerhouse.)
(China dominated early on...)
(with their physical advantage.)
(With Korea struggling to keep up,)
(My Star stole the ball from Yao Ming.)
(His basket sparked a comeback,)
(but China kept scoring.)
(25 seconds left, Korea: 83, China: 90)
He runs to the basket and finishes.
(Hyun Joo Yup's 2-pointer, Korea: 85, China: 90)
- It's a tie! - It's a tie!
(Moon Kyung Eun's 3-pointer, Korea: 88, China: 90)
(4.7 seconds left, Korea: 90, China: 90)
(They pulled off a dramatic comeback and sent the game into overtime.)
(Right at the start of overtime)
He finishes it.
(My Star hit a 3-point.)
(In a miraculous comeback, they won the gold medal.)
(My Star)
It wasn't just me. The other players did a great job.
So...
(He even shed tears, something he rarely did.)
I got...
really emotional.
I understand why you cried.
I thought Korea would lose,
so I wasn't watching. When I turned on the TV later,
I realized the score was actually pretty close.
And we won.
It made me emotional too.
You were the one out there playing and winning the game,
so it must've been an emotional moment.
I got emotional...
because I made the national team when I was a freshman in college,
right after graduating from high school.
From the time I became a national team athlete...
to 2002 was exactly 10 years.
We went ten years...
without a single win.
(We went 20 years without a single win against China.)
It was an era when a lot of great players...
came up at the same time on our side too.
I felt bad for our fans.
That day,
we finally defeated...
China's elite team for the first time.
You're really amazing.
How's Korean basketball these days?
Are they as good...
as you were when you won the Asian Games?
There are quite a number of great players.
There are quite a number.
We have a lot of players at a similar level...
across every position.
It's a golden generation.
(Korean basketball is in its golden era.)
(One month later at the Nagoya Asian Games)
(The new golden generation proved its worth.)
(Beating Japan in the final,)
(they claimed the gold medal.)
(The golden generation continues.)
(The basketball legend's prediction came true!)
(Glancing)
Look at the clouds.
It's amazing.
(Raising the sunshade for a better look outside)
This place...
- We're up on the mountain. - It's...
Because of the high altitude...
How does that...
(My Star surprisingly likes nature.)
It's like a painting here.
(It's like a painting here.)
(Jang Hoon is unexpectedly pure.)
Goodness.
I never cared for such things when I was younger.
As I get older,
I find mountains beautiful...
(My Star's heart grows younger with age.)
I came to Wonju last week.
I'm coming to Gangwon Province two weeks in a row.
- You filmed this show in Wonju? - Yes.
Last week,
I went to a fishcake factory.
That's my favorite.
- You fold it and skewer it. - You skewer it.
I've been to all the factories through this show.
Chicken factory,
(Chicken factory)
bread factory,
(Bread factory)
shoe factory...
(Shoe factory)
So you mostly visit people...
- in manufacturing. - That's right.
I have to travel around the country every week.
Every week, I meet really amazing people.
People who work hard.
They're hardworking,
and they do a lot of good too.
There are many people who are like that.
I got here to film the show,
but I learn a lot too.
(My Star learns from millionaires with big hearts and deep pockets.)
So,
it's already been two years.
It's already been two years?
Yes.
It's probably close to 100 episodes.
That's a lot.
How many shows are you on now, My Star?
Around eight.
- Eight? - Yes.
Big brother.
My lord.
Let's go together.
Well...
(There he goes again.)
I'm probably...
the only one in Korea...
who's been on this many long-running shows.
(That's true.)
The shows I'm on that have been running for over ten years...
How many are they?
"Mom's Diary" has been running for over ten years.
"Mom's Diary."
That's the signature show of SBS.
"Same Bed, Different Dreams..."
- is almost reaching 10 years. - It's almost been 10 years.
- It's almost been ten years. - Really?
"Men on a Mission" has been running for more than ten years.
"Ask Us Anything Fortune Teller" has been running for seven years.
Goodness.
Even "Divorce Camp,"
one of the shows...
I'm known for these days,
- "Divorce Camp." - is already in its third year.
They're all hit shows.
I was really lucky.
- He's got great stamina. - That's right.
We get tired really quickly.
He doesn't get tired.
I don't get tired even if I don't eat.
Right.
- Right. - I think that's my strength.
I should speak honestly...
from a viewer's perspective.
I thought I should speak honestly.
People often cast me...
because of that.
If I join their show...
You'd bring good energy.
They think the show could run for a long time.
Long-running...
I said this when I met Jang Hoon before.
It was when he had just started appearing on shows.
I thought he was the funniest.
Even on variety shows. So I told him,
"You're the funniest person I know."
And he was like, "Hey, you're the funniest to me."
(Fellow thinkers share the same sense of humor.)
Kwang Kyu.
- Kwang Kyu. - Yes?
We're a bit late.
Should I speed up?
A bit...
- Okay. - I think we'd need to speed up.
This car...
- has a really smooth ride. - Yes.
It's nice.
(Today's driver Kwang Kyu...)
(has been driving nonstop...)
(for 3 hours.)
(On the longest drive yet)
The massage...
- Is it good? - It's a proper one.
Try it too.
(My Star is enjoying a comfortable ride thanks to Kwang Kyu.)
Hello. I'm Seo Jang Hoon's manager.
We'll be there in five minutes.
(Seo Genie is in charge of communicating with the crew.)
(The travel duties are now perfectly divided.)
- Three minutes. - Okay.
(The secretaries are surprisingly reliable.)
Is it this place?
It's here.
So this is the place.
(They reached the filming location...)
(of "Seo Jang Hoon's Millionaire Next Door.")
We've made it.
- Thank you. - We've made it.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you.
(Time: 1pm, Location: Studio, Details: Studio filming)
(They arrived in time thanks to Kwang Kyu.)
Goodness.
Hello.
They didn't let the cars go in front of the tunnel.
Great work.
(Seo Jin stepped out too.)
- This is Seo Jin. Say hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Showing his capitalist dimples)
- Say hello. - Hello. Nice to meet you.
(Jang Ye Won, co-host of "Seo Jang Hoon's Millionaire Next Door")
Hello.
(Seo Genie is meeting Ye Won for the first time.)
- It's been a while. - It has.
I saw you, but I forgot.
- Right. - Jang Hoon...
- Because he's too tall. - Yes.
- I look small. - I'm sorry.
- You've become prettier. - We're on it together.
- How do you know her? - We...
- We've seen each other around. - We've seen each other around.
How does he know everyone?
(Fortunately, Older Bestie is rich in connections.)
- We have to start filming. - Yes.
There's something you should check.
There's nothing for you to take care of.
So first,
I'm coming...
to Gangneung for the first time in a really long while.
After the filming of the show ends,
let's do a mini tour around Gangneung.
- A mini tour? - Yes.
Let's do that.
A mini tour around Gangneung.
Could you put together a schedule?
(My Star suddenly requests a tour around Gangneung.)
(When was the last time you went on a trip?)
Well...
I'm not sure.
I film shows...
all week.
Looking at the waves at a beach...
(It's been ages since he last sat back and enjoyed the sea.)
isn't so easy these days.
I only have the memory of coming here when I was really young.
So I wanted...
to experience this region a little.
Could you put together a schedule?
- A mini tour? - Yes.
A compact tour around Gangneung.
Great food and attractions.
Things like that.
A mini tour.
The best food,
sights,
and activities.
A short one. You...
- also don't like long trips. - I don't.
We can make it quick.
How many locations do you want to go?
I told you.
A simple one.
Somewhere with good food,
sights,
and activities.
Eat,
bite, and chew.
- Taste. - Taste.
Please do that for me.
A simple one.
Gyeongpodae is famous in Gangneung.
I really like Gyeongpodae.
I went to the Gyeongpo Beach...
when I was eight.
I've never been there since.
Gyeongpodae is nice.
There's a place I like.
Something like that.
Gyeongpodae.
(Young Master seems to know what he's doing.)
I like the sea.
Gyeongpodae.
Let's have dinner by the sea at Gyeongpodae.
Seo Jin is great at these things.
Okay. We'll go in now.
(It's happening today. Will it be okay?)
(The filming begins after they're left with a big mission.)
Okay.
(Will we be able to do it before the filming ends?)
When you go to Gyeongpodae,
- there's S Hotel. - Yes.
It's newly built, and the view is great.
We can have a cup of tea there.
Is it run by your friend?
(Is it run by your friend?)
Yes.
There's the beach there.
There's a restaurant I go to...
in Gyeongpodae.
- Really? - There's a restaurant.
Good.
We can go there...
and have some raw fish and...
(Having a drink with some raw fish)
(My Star, the angry giant...)
(who yells all day long...)
(becomes a bright sunny character?)
(What did they prepare?)
(Not angry Jang Hoon,)
(but an 8-year-old giant kid)
One, two.
It's like a family photo.
(Will My Genie Secretary's Mini Tour end successfully?)
(The millionaire My Star came to meet a millionaire.)
- This place... - There are many things here.
It's a workshop.
There are so many books over there as well.
I'm not sure if the air conditioner is on,
or if this is a freezer storage.
- It's cool in here. - It's very cool in here.
(The secretaries are right behind him.)
(Moving carefully)
(They join quietly so they don't disturb the filming.)
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
- Hello. - Welcome.
- Come this way. - Come this way.
You can tell right away...
that he fits right in...
with the artwork here.
Choi Ok Yeong,
today's millionaire.
Yes. I think the art museum and the artworks...
make me a millionaire.
You have three art museums?
I've never seen anyone with three art museums.
- An artist. - Yes.
- Your name is... - Choi Ok Yeong.
Choi Ok Yeong.
Do you know art?
(Shaking his head)
You don't? But you're a New Yorker.
What does that have to do with this?
I know the expensive ones.
Aren't there many art museums in New York?
There are many galleries.
What's the price of their statues?
- It was... - It was 1.25 million dollars.
- It was 1.25 million dollars? - Yes.
Really? Back then?
(The New Yorker is surprised.)
We have to be careful.
- What? - We have to be careful.
(Seo Jin's eyes have changed.)
(Kwang Kyu, next to the nervous Young Master...)
(Yawning)
(He keeps yawning because of the long drive.)
(He tries to focus on My Star...)
(Yawning)
(Pretending like he's looking at the painting)
If you create too many works, their values in the future...
(While Seo Jin's eyes are wide open,)
might drop.
(he keeps hiding and trying to hold back his yawns.)
(Feeling embarrassed)
(Stop yawning!)
My belly is quite big.
(Changing the subject)
I had gamjatang late last night.
- What? - At what time?
Around 10pm.
You had gamjatang at 10pm?
You're really something.
(He's a millionaire when it comes to belly fat.)
(Hitting)
Should I hit it?
(Exclaiming)
(Glaring)
(It's trouble if My Star gets angry.)
(This is because of you!)
Managers, the apron...
Please get the apron, managers.
I need an apron.
(My Star requested an apron.)
Where is the apron? Is the apron here?
(He starts looking for it.)
Is it here?
Apron...
Don't you have an apron?
The apron.
(Here's the apron.)
(He gets Ye Won's apron too.)
- This is uncomfortable. - My Star.
Kwang Kyu.
- Why are you just leaving? - That's right.
It doesn't have a tie.
It's too short.
Does it fit him?
Didn't you wear it the other way around?
(Did he get Giant My Star a regular apron?)
It's too short.
(Not a chance)
This...
(Feeling uncomfortable)
(Even Seo Jin, who was watching, looks flustered.)
- It has a tie, but... - It has a tie.
- It's too short. - It's...
The size...
- The size... - It won't work.
- Okay. I'll just use this. - We'll just carry on.
It doesn't matter.
I'm sorry!
(Loudly)
(He got out of trouble with a passionate apology.)
(But My Star's apron...)
(kept slipping off throughout the shoot.)
He got very flustered because his son was so bad at painting.
But he still has the genes.
(Is the apron small or is Jang Hoon big?)
This is interesting.
(Kwang Kyu is taking a look around the workshop.)
(Feeling a little scared)
This wouldn't be real, right?
(Hitting)
You startled me.
Hey...
Hey. Gosh.
(Another thrilling day of teasing older bestie)
- Kwang Kyu. - Yes?
Where are we going to go later?
- What? - Where are we going later?
Shall we sit here?
Let's sit here and plan.
(They're running out of time.)
(They quickly have a meeting outside the filming studio.)
- Could you look up... - Yes?
things to do in Gangneung.
Let's do the research.
Gangneung's hot places.
(The search begins.)
(The best food, sights, and activities)
(They have to plan a full itinerary with three quick stops.)
Why is my face coming up?
(Face?)
Why is my face here?
Search...
Why is my face showing up when I'm searching?
(Famous tourist spots in Gangneung)
(Do I have the face of a king of Gangneung?)
Why is my face coming up?
Hey.
Why is my face showing up when I'm searching?
(While Kwang Kyu is lost in the world of technology...)
This place is still there.
Busan Raw Fish Restaurant.
(Busan Raw Fish Restaurant.)
- Kwang Kyu. - Yes?
It's a favorite spot of presidents and business leaders.
- Where? - Here.
I've known the place for so many years.
When did you last visit the place?
I went there even in my 20s.
- Let's go to Gyeongpodae, - Yes.
have some beer at S Hotel...
S Hotel has a great view.
(A place with a view that Seo Jin approves)
It was newly built.
It's located on a cliff,
so it's got a great view.
(They'll tick off "best sight" at a hotel by the sea.)
Then we'll eat...
(A raw fish restaurant by the sea)
at Busan Raw Fish Restaurant with the view of the sea.
We'll have raw fish and soju.
Raw fish and crabs.
I want to do everything at Gyeongpodae.
From there, we can go to the Gyeongpo Beach.
Lee Seo Jin...
knew the route he took...
so many times when he used to date before.
Everything was planned out...
in his head at once.
I heard it was where you used to go when you were dating. Is that true?
What does he know?
(What does he know?)
I know who it is,
but I can't say who.
(Believe it or not)
We wouldn't need to make a reservation, right?
Shouldn't we call them and talk about it?
I'll call them.
(Calling the hotel lounge first)
Hello, this is S Hotel.
Why does my face keep coming up?
(He still doesn't know its function.)
Hello, this is S Hotel restaurant's Lee So Yeon.
Hello.
- Hello. - Thanks for your time.
Do you perhaps know Lee Seo Jin?
(Do you perhaps know Lee Seo Jin?)
- Lee Seo Jin? - Yes.
Lee Seo Jin...
Is he someone who works at our restaurant?
No, I'm sorry.
This is a show called My Genie Secretary.
I'm calling to ask for permission to film at your restaurant.
I'm afraid we wouldn't be able to decide that at our restaurant.
I'll connect you to the marketing team.
Please connect me to the marketing team.
Yes, please hold.
(It's not a great start.)
Are we going to the restaurant?
(Listening to the ringing for a long time)
Do I have to press a number?
Press what?
Hello?
- Hello, how can I help you? - Yes, hello.
- Yes. - Is this the marketing team?
- Yes, hello. - Yes, hello.
We're SBS' My Genie Secretary.
Yes.
I'm Kim Kwang Kyu. Hello.
- Yes, hello. - Hello.
- Yes. - Do you know me?
- Yes. Is this real? - Thank you.
Yes, it's real.
Yes. I'm Kim Kwang Kyu, a singer of two albums.
We're filming in Gangneung right now.
- Yes. - Yes, would it...
be possible to film at your hotel?
- Do you mean today? - Pardon?
- Are you filming today? - Yes.
- What time would it be? - Pardon?
What time were you planning to come?
Between 6:30pm to 7:30pm.
How many people will be joining you?
If that would be inconvenient, we can bring fewer people.
If you film here,
what's it going to be about?
Oh, we're just...
stopping by randomly...
- while visiting the area. - I see.
We do have a reservation for 70 people in the buffet today.
But we'll be able to make room for you.
Really?
A buffet? Are you sure that place is to watch scenery?
Of course.
Then...
Ask her if we can see the scenery there.
- Can you hold for a second? - Yes.
Lee Seo Jin has something to say.
- Okay. - Hello.
- Hello. - Is it possible...
to get a table by the scenery?
- Okay. - Even if we don't eat,
can we still have a drink or something?
Oh, then do you mean when you come in...
you'd have tea in the lounge...
- Yes. - instead of a meal?
But I'd prefer...
somewhere with a nice view.
It doesn't have to be a restaurant.
Even the lobby lounge is fine.
- Okay. I understand. - Yes.
I'll check and get back to you.
- Thank you. Bye. - Bye.
I think she sounded positive.
(Smirking)
What?
You're turning 60 soon,
and is that the best you can say?
You said you used to work as a real estate agent.
That's why I never got to sign any contract.
I see why.
"Do you know My Genie Secretary?"
(The older bestie is high maintenance.)
(He got a call.)
- Hello? - Hello.
Hi.
(Did the hotel approve?)
It seems possible.
- Really? - You can come in at 6:30pm.
Yes, we'll be there...
by 6:30pm. Thank you.
- Thank you. Bye. - Bye.
(My Genie Secretary's mini tour)
Jang Hoon.
- Jang Hoon. - They look the same.
They look the same.
(Did you call me?)
I agree.
They have the same eyes, don't they?
(Eyes just as cute as My Star's)
Jang Hoon.
Yes.
(Standing up)
(My Star suddenly appears.)
- He's done. - I'm done.
- He's done. - Are you done?
- Yes. - Let's move.
We're going to the gallery now.
- Are we moving now? - Yes.
Have you been monitoring?
We have.
Then we left when you were drawing.
When I was drawing? Was there anything that stood out...
until then?
(My Star's sharp question)
- It's perfect. - It's perfect.
- Yes. - If there's any problem,
- it's all your fault. - Never.
There will never be a problem.
I've said...
(Jumping)
- There's a bug. - Okay.
(A bug on My neat Star?)
- There really is one. - A bug.
Bend down. He can't reach it.
- A spider? - Hey, you do it.
(Restless after seeing a bug 2m high)
Bend down. He can't reach it.
(Blowing)
(Aiming)
(Neatly removing the bug)
- You hit it like this. - Okay.
It was on your head.
So...
it's over after one lap.
- It's only this big. - So?
Are you going to wash your hands or not?
Oh, that's...
(My Star got ink on his hands while drawing.)
The wet wipe won't do it.
(What's it going to be?)
Go wash your hands in the restroom.
Let me think about it.
Okay.
Did you touch something?
I don't like to use restrooms outside.
- As much as possible. - That's ink.
But it was pretty clean.
I'm okay so far.
There was soap too.
(My Star's down.)
(On eggshells)
I'll wait for you in the car.
(Moving)
(Seo Genie gets in the driver's seat.)
(Setting the optimal indoor temperature)
(Next)
(Grabbing the schedule)
(Setting the GPS)
(Kwang Kyu is waiting to serve My Star.)
(Spotting the Lord)
- See you. - Nice to meet you.
See you soon.
(Bowing at their backs)
(The Lord appears.)
(Dashing)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Serving before My Star gets upset)
- You should go the other way. - I'm only opening the door for you.
- My Star. - You don't have to do that.
I have to.
- You don't have to do that. - It's my job.
- Gosh. - Oh, gosh.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
(Setting off in good mood)
(Silence in the car)
(Glancing)
(When he's down, show him cute videos or pirctures.)
I heard you like to see babies when you're tired.
- Babies... - Who is that?
Babies...
(Good job, Kwang Kyu.)
My friend had a housewarming party the other day.
His youngest is so cute.
(Playing a cute video)
(Laughing)
He got food all over his clothes.
Look at what he's doing.
Gosh.
I wish I had a child.
- Don't you? - Yes.
(Glancing)
Do you have a nephew or a niece?
I do. I have...
two nieces.
But we're not that close.
(The doting uncle feels bad for him.)
They went to study in Canada after going to middle school.
- You don't get to see them often. - No.
The oldest got into UCLA.
The youngest is going to college this year.
I don't get to see them. They're abroad.
(Coy)
You should get married soon.
(The conversation ends with marriage.)
Here we are.
Is this the gallery?
(5pm, Haslla Art World)
It's bigger than I thought.
(It's about 109,090m² wide.)
(There are terrific sculptures everywhere.)
That's a cool sculpture.
Check this out.
It's huge.
It's cool.
Look at the boat.
- It's incredible. - Look at that.
The sea...
(Exclaiming)
Awesome.
It's basically floating in the sea.
(What surprised My Star?)
- Oh, what is that? - That's Jeongdongjin.
I know.
This is amazing.
(Before My Star's eyes...)
This is awesome.
(lies the endless Gangneung sea.)
This place is awesome.
(The East Sea clears your mind just by looking at it.)
Awesome.
- Awesome. - Awesome.
I'm scared.
(The beautiful sight excites My Star.)
I didn't expect to see this view at all.
This is unimaginable.
This place is the best.
When I was 7 or 8,
Gyeongpodae was the first place my family visited on a trip.
It means so much to me.
I think this is the first time...
(Back to Gangneung after 44 years)
after eight.
It feels like I'm abroad.
- Hey. - You know?
It's worth coming here.
It feels like I'm abroad.
(My Star is back to 8.)
I could only see this in Hawaii or...
This is even better than Hawaii.
I haven't seen such a wide view like this.
This is basically the Pacific Ocean, isn't it?
It is.
I couldn't believe...
I could see such a vast ocean...
in the country.
I got a lot on my mind.
I thought...
I should see something like this more often.
I was very happy.
This place is...
(The wonderful sight made My Star speechless.)
(Don't forget to take pictures.)
Right. Pictures.
(My Genie Secretary's official photographer)
My Star.
(Thumbs up)
(2m-tall boy giant)
- Give me the camera. - No, let's take it together.
One, two, three.
(This is the romantic height difference.)
Let me take your picture.
- Go stand. - Thank you.
(He likes unique poses.)
(Polite legs)
(I'll be a millionaire one day.)
- Cool. - It's incredible.
- It's the best. - It's wonderful.
You really are rich.
Hey.
- He's even richer than you are. - Oh, no.
- I'm nothing. - True.
(The place that touches My Star...)
I'm jealous.
(and makes him modest at the same time)
You can face outside.
(Seo Jin found a place to wait.)
This way.
- It's crazy. - What?
- I love this place. - The view is...
It's all gallery outside.
It's 495,867m²...
(My Star bumps into the light.)
(Watch out for My Star's height.)
It's 495,867m²...
Oh, no.
- Hey. - It scared me.
Hey.
Hey. Gosh.
- I can't believe you touched it. - But...
I can't believe you touched it.
It's pretty low.
That's low?
(Flustered)
Hey. You call that low? Gosh.
Jang Hoon, do you want something to eat?
How about some tea?
- Okay. - Chamomela...
- Chamomela... - No...
I want yuzu tea or something.
- Hot? - Yes.
- Can I order here? - Yes.
One hot yuzu tea and...
Can I also get it cold?
(Grabbing)
(A blanket appears.)
(Taking out a blanket for My Star)
Put this on.
It's wool, so it doesn't feel sticky even when it's humid.
- Isn't this a blanket? - What?
You can use it as a blanket or...
you can use it as a sheet.
(Happy to put it on)
It's big,
but it looks small on you.
It looks small, doesn't it?
It might feel too heavy if you use it as a blanket.
So if you use it as a sheet,
it's really warm...
and it's not sticky.
It's perfect.
It's nice.
It's soft.
(He can't stop touching it.)
(5pm, Haslla Art World)
This place is...
(My Star's back to filming after a short break.)
really huge.
I didn't know about this place.
(Watching without getting in the way)
By the way,
it must've been a lot of work...
to create that path.
(Tapping)
(What's that sound?)
I'm a bayonet instructor, you idiot.
Bring it on.
(A match between a 55-year-old and a 58-year-old)
(Never looked so happy today)
(While the secretaries are having a good time...)
(What on earth are they doing?)
Is this gallery...
funded by admission fees?
(My Star continues hosting.)
Show me your bayonet skills.
(Suddenly turning into the bayonet instructor)
(The sergeant first class' sharp moves)
(Happy to see his older bestie's talent)
Take this.
(While they're having a good time...)
Okay.
(My Star is irritated.)
I had to...
listen to other people talking.
And they kept getting on my nerves.
(They kept getting on my nerves.)
It's slippery.
- It's slippery. - Exactly.
(The secretaries are taking their time to check out the gallery.)
(They look like...)
(an old couple on a trip.)
Look at that.
(Honey, look at that.)
(The old lady who is still young at heart takes a picture.)
(My husband's back)
(The old man is serious about cleaning.)
(The old lady likes cats.)
(They make a perfect couple.)
They look after each other so much.
(They look after each other so much.)
They look after each other...
more than they look after me.
Okay.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- It's over. - Thank you for your time.
That was fast.
(Rushing to greet My Star)
Come here.
- Me? - Do you...
have to go back to Seoul or do you have time?
- To join you? - Yes.
Can I?
Stay for lunch. Don't go yet.
- Yes, join us for the meal. - Yes.
Right.
- She's also from my agency. - Yes.
- It's the same agency. - Yes.
Let's go together in one car.
Gosh.
- Gosh. - Let's go.
- Well done. - Thank you.
(6pm, mini tour by secretaries with Jang Ye Won)
This is nice.
This place is really nice.
(Mini tour by secretaries for My Star)
Look at the sea.
(Excited already)
Ye Won, where did you first meet Kwang Kyu?
Where did we first meet?
- I don't know. - We met a lot on the way.
I remember sitting next to you in a wedding.
- Whose wedding? - Who was it?
Right. Was it Kangnam?
I think it was Kangnam's wedding.
I got the bouquet, right?
- You're all linked. - Yes.
Is this your first time meeting Seo Jin?
Please drop the honorifics.
- But... - Feel free.
It's my first time seeing him in my whole life.
- Really? - Yes.
- We didn't have a chance. - We didn't have a chance.
(Meeting Lee Seo Jin for the first time in her life)
Who found the restaurant?
They found it.
I asked them for a mini tour.
Because it's been a while since I last visited Gangneung.
Something to see,
watch,
and enjoy.
I asked them for those things. That's what we're going to do.
Yes. So...
we're going to check out Ojukheon House.
Jang Hoon knows a lot about history.
After Ojukheon House?
Then...
the best hotel in Gyeongpodae is S Hotel.
Isn't that place known...
- for the view? - It's the best.
Because it's standing on the cliff.
We'll have...
drinks there...
and enjoy the view.
And...
the sashimi restaurant I went in my 20s is...
still around.
In Gyeongpodae.
It's known...
to be a favorite of former presidents and chairmen.
That's how it's known.
Really?
When they're not actually open today?
They weren't going to open today.
That's amazing.
(Today's course)
(Ojukheon House, Gyeongpodae, sashimi restaurant)
I'm getting high expectations.
(You may look forward to it.)
(Ojukheon House, Gyeongpo Lake, current location)
(S Hotel)
(Sashimi Restaurant)
(Staring)
(He can't stop looking outside.)
This place has...
a magnificent view.
It's wonderful.
- Right here. - It's nice.
I get to check out Gangneung.
It's nice.
(Rolling down the window)
It's a good place for a honeymoon.
(The autumn Gangneung sea catches My Star's attention.)
Look at the sea.
There's a seawall at the end.
I see a lighthouse.
There's everything.
Does it lead to downtown?
We're heading to Gangneung.
We're near Gangneung.
- From Jeongdongjin? - That's right.
(They're near downtown Gangneung.)
This must be downtown, right?
- This is totally... - This is...
- my first time coming here. - Really?
- You had no chance to come. - Aside from...
visiting Gyeongpodae with my family...
when I was young...
- Gyeongpodae. - Isn't that way too long ago?
When you were eight?
- When I was eight. - That was so long ago.
All I remember is Gyeongpodae when I was eight.
(Redrawing his memories of Gangneung when he was 8)
- Hey. That's... - That's cool.
What is that?
- There's all kinds of stuff. - What is that?
- What is this place? - That's cool. What's that?
It's a fishing area.
It's not a fishing area. It looks like a cafe.
- It looks like a cafe. - I think...
you can eat there on the water.
It keeps changing.
It says luna in Spanish.
I think it's a floating cafe.
In the middle...
What's inside the ball?
I think it's a park.
- What is that? - That's cool.
I visited it when I was really young.
Everything looked fascinating after so long.
(While driving here and there,)
(it became dark.)
It's pretty late.
I think we'll have to see Ojukheon House...
in the car.
I think we'll just pass by.
Then...
why don't you tell us about Ojukheon House?
Since you know a lot about history.
You know...
that's where Yi Yul Gok was born, right?
Yes. That's about all I know.
That is Shin Saimdang's...
parents' house.
I think when she got pregnant...
with Yi Yul Gok...
- She gave birth. - She gave birth there.
It's the only family in this country...
to have two members...
appear in the banknotes.
(Mother and son in the banknotes are unprecedented in the world.)
(Building historical knowledge)
All you need to see in Ojukheon House is...
the black bamboos.
(Excited to see black bamboos)
It's Ojukheon House.
(Arriving in Ojukheon House even before they know it)
Oh, Ojukheon House.
So this is Ojukheon House.
(Excited)
(Looking around)
When did it get this big?
- It's huge. - The place...
It's really big inside.
I don't remember there being gates and all in the past.
Was the house always this big?
I mean during the Joseon dynasty.
It's huge.
It's big, and the inside is much bigger.
Are we inside a military headquarters?
My gosh, look at the size of the gate.
(Looking around will take some time.)
Wait.
What is it?
(It's closed.)
It's blocked.
What?
(Walking on eggshells)
Ojukheon House is closed.
We can't take a look inside.
(Closed for the day)
Do they not have a night tour or something?
(Flustered)
It's my fault.
I didn't think it would be blocked off...
by such a huge gate.
Let's take a photo before we leave in front of Ojukheon House.
- What? - Let's take a photo or something.
- Take one in front of the gate. - Okay.
- Let's do that. - I'll take it for you.
We took the trouble to come all the way here.
We can just take one here in front.
- Yes. - Let's get a shot here in front.
It's in Chinese characters.
(My Star keeps walking?)
(Bummed out, they peek inside.)
- You have to walk straight in. - The black bamboos...
- aren't near the gate. - No.
You can't see them.
We have to walk inside.
(They drove all the way to Ojukheon House to see the black bamboos.)
Since we came to Ojukheon House,
I really wanted to see the black bamboos.
It was such a shame, but still.
This is my first time at Ojukheon House.
I don't recall when I did either.
It's your first time, and yet it's closed.
Ojukheon House.
Let's take a commemorative photo here.
- Okay. - Good.
Ojukheon House!
- It's meaningful, isn't it? - Yes, it is.
What matters is that we stopped by.
Let's go.
But there are no black bamboos...
near the gate. It must be inside.
(Thinking)
There are bamboos over there.
(Spotted bamboos)
- Where? - On the side.
(Are they the black bamboos?)
But the bamboo isn't black.
The stems have to be black.
- What? - The stems have to be black.
- They're not black. - The stems aren't black.
(Bummed out)
They should be black.
- Is it... - I found a black one!
hard to tell because it's dark?
Is it dead?
- I found one! - He found it.
I finally found one.
(Smiling brightly after finding the long-awaited black bamboos)
- It's a black bamboo. - I found a black bamboo.
This right here is black bamboo.
- There are more over here. - Where?
- Where? - Over here.
- Where? We hit the jackpot! - Black bamboo.
- A black bamboo. - We hit the jackpot.
This right here is the black bamboo.
(Happy)
(I was dying to see you.)
Because black bamboos are nearby,
it's only natural to be here.
There's no way they'd only be in there.
My gosh. Goodness.
It's a first.
I was hoping to get a glimpse of black bamboos,
and coincidentally,
Kwang Kyu said, "It's here!"
I was so happy to see them.
At least we found meaning in visiting Ojukheon House.
(Making memories and finding meaning along the way)
At first,
I thought it was a dead tree.
I was like, "Is it a dead tree?"
But from the side, the leaves looked alive.
It was so fascinating.
I turned on the flash in a flash.
He was over the moon.
- A black bamboo. - We hit the jackpot.
Jang Hoon may be big in size, but he's still a boy.
He may have had a divorce, but he's still a boy.
- What? - What was that?
Let's go!
- He... - Let's go.
- He's so cold-hearted. - At least we saw black bamboos.
- Yes, we saw black bamboos. - Exactly.
- It was a meaningful trip. - Yes.
Where would you...
Black bamboos are rare. You can hardly ...
- True. - see them around.
- Having seen them is what matters. - Of course.
- We even touched them. - Right.
- You even touched them? - Some are over there.
- You must've received good energy. - Gosh.
- People simply take photos... - Yes?
at whatever photo spots.
- Photos last forever. - Right.
(Took photos and saw the black bamboos)
- Gosh. - Goodness. It was...
(It's a relief we got to see the black bamboos.)
Where are we off to next?
- The hotel? - Gyeongpodae.
- Hotel. - Yes, hotel.
(Hotel lounge in front of Gyeongpodae)
Gangneung has a lot to offer.
Isn't it fun hanging out after work?
Yes, people should...
- Take trips? - take trips...
and such.
After work, we're too busy...
- trying to get back home. - True.
We always go home the moment work ends.
That's true.
(My Star is quite pleased with the mini tour.)
How nice.
It's nice here.
We're in Gyeongpodae.
- What's that? - Isn't that where we're heading to?
- Aren't I right? - Is that where we're going?
- Yes. - Yes.
(This is not sponsored.)
The view must be incredible.
(A sightseeing tour of the whole Gyeongpodae)
It's huge.
I have a feeling it'll have a really nice view.
Where's the coffee shop?
It's in the first-floor lobby.
First-floor lobby?
- First-floor lobby? - The lobby.
The lobby. I...
I thought it'd be high up, but it's in the first-floor lobby.
The lower floor is better here.
So the lower floors are nicer.
(Feeling self-conscious for no reason)
Where is it?
(The coffee shop with a nice view)
- Where do we go? - Which way is it?
Over there.
(Anxious)
The bar is on the left.
But it's not...
- Bar? - Bar?
- Is it the bar? - Bar?
(The view should be good, right?)
Do you work here?
- Yes. - Which way is it?
- This way. - Okay.
Is it the lounge?
You can go to the lounge...
or sit over there.
You can't see much at night.
The lounge is good.
The view is...
- You can't see anything. - It's right over there.
The ocean is right in front.
- It's... - You can see it...
- right up ahead. - I see.
- Okay. - Nice.
Shall we sit here?
I have a feeling there are usually seats outside.
- But it rained. - There must've been tables.
Do you want to go outside?
Are we going outside? Okay.
(The Giant Boy wants to see the night ocean.)
(The Gyeongpo ocean glows quietly in the darkness.)
The sound of waves.
(Seo Jin checks first, just to be safe.)
(We came all this way.)
(We can't leave without seeing the night ocean.)
You can see the ocean directly from here.
This must be...
I love how close we are to it.
The sound of waves is loud and clear.
(Gyeongpo at night is tranquil, unlike the daytime vibrancy.)
My gosh, it's nice.
It's nice here.
(Secretaries' Mini Tour: Ojukheon House)
The emptiness with nothing around makes it all the better.
- You can clearly see the waves. - The waves are beautiful.
(Even the Giant is moved by nature's greater grandeur.)
(Seeing My Star satisfied, Seo Genie relaxes and enjoys the moment, too.)
Walk down here, and it's Gyeongpodae.
You'll find sashimi places.
- It's next to each other. - Yes.
Except for when I went on a family trip to...
Gyeongpodae Beach.
I was eight years old.
(Back at Gyeongpo for the first time in years, since childhood)
Seeing the sandy beach...
and the waves altogether right in front of me...
made me happy. It was delightful.
If I were to come here to relax,
and not for work...
- Can you come here alone? - I can totally come alone.
- Really? - Don't you want to?
I keep thinking...
I should go on trips...
before I grow much older.
He won't stop talking about it.
The kind of life he'll live for the rest of his life.
It's a common topic for us.
By the way, he's mellowed out a lot after becoming an entertainer.
- Right? - Me?
Yes. In the past...
He's become much nicer.
- Really? - Yes.
Becoming an entertainer was one thing.
- Right. - The biggest reason was me...
- What is it? - Getting older.
- Older? - Yes.
- That's sad to hear. - Growing old mellowed me out...
compared to when I was younger.
In the past, Jang Hoon had a fierce look in his eyes.
I don't know the days when he played basketball.
But I saw a lot of videos of him.
He was no joke.
The memes are all about him...
- The memes. - getting angry.
A lot of the memes are of him getting angry.
(Jang Hoon was fearless in his days as an athlete.)
He was full of anger.
His face was scary when he had just started...
- Really? - variety shows.
Sitting next to him was...
He has mellowed out.
- A lot at that. - It's only natural.
I'm being really careful...
and thinking a lot before I speak.
- Is that so? - He's really thorough.
We hung out together last time.
Everyone was surprised.
He analyzed all the variety shows.
He analyzes all of them.
- Who? - Jang Hoon.
(My Star thoroughly analyzes variety shows.)
How's My Genie Secretary?
Do it. Analyze My Genie Secretary.
Where could they improve on?
- Improve on? - Yes.
There's nothing to improve. Just do it.
(What?)
Didn't I sound just like Seo Jin?
(Feeling guilty)
(I'm not full of energy. I just do it.)
(There's nothing to improve. Just do it.)
That was good.
Here's what...
surprises me.
When Seo Jin says this on shows,
I think, "He's saying exactly what I want to."
From what I can see,
he has the most similar tendencies to me.
- I agree with that. - But personally, I think...
I'm a warmer-hearted person.
(Jang Hoon's thoughts)
I'm sure that's what Seo Jin thinks too.
- Totally. - I'm a warmer-hearted person.
We're quite alike, but I'm a warmer-hearted person.
That's what I say.
Who do you think has a warmer heart?
- Right now? - Yes.
- Jang Hoon is much warmer. - I told you.
- Really? - Yes.
- I... - Just look at his posture.
- I... - Just look at him.
- That posture is one of a kind. - Look at his posture.
Both he and I are thinkers.
We're extreme thinkers.
But I'm a warm thinker.
(Warm thinker)
- But... - You're totally right.
- There's no warm thinker. - He's right.
- No, they exist. - They do.
- A warm thinker? - A warm thinker.
He's a cranky thinker.
Seo Jin is...
- He's secretly sweet. - A secretly sweet thinker.
But I'm not that good at being secretly sweet.
(All thinkers are different.)
Even when criticizing something,
Jang Hoon tries to cheer you up.
- Is that so? - Yes.
He walks on eggshells after saying things.
- I filter my words. - He does.
- Seo Jin doesn't. - So...
Seo Jin... But either way,
he doesn't care about filtering...
his words or not.
True.
(He gave up.)
Seo Jin doesn't hold back.
He's got it easy.
(Easygoing because he's got it easy)
You're right. Seo Jin is a cold thinker,
- while I'm a hot thinker. - A hot thinker?
- What's with a hot thinker? - Maybe not hot.
(Cold Thinker Seo Jin)
- A hot thinker? - A warm thinker.
- A warm thinker. - I'm a warm thinker.
(Cleaning up)
- A hot thinker. - A warm thinker.
- A hot thinker moment. - A warm thinker.
- Let's go. - Let's get sashimi.
(Filling the seat with warmth)
- Let's go in. - Shall we?
- Are you ready? - Go in.
Nice.
The ocean is right in front.
- Hi. - Hi.
(Showing off those dimples)
It's so nice to see you.
- You haven't visited in forever. - No, I haven't.
You must be the owner of this place.
Yes.
I've been coming here since I was young.
- Really? - Really?
- Since your 20s, right? - Yes.
(Seo Jin is here as a secretary today.)
(Looking around)
I haven't been here for years.
Are you lost in memories?
I'm just amazed this place is still open.
(Full of memories)
Why are you tearing up? Is it bringing back memories?
He's crying. Seo Jin is crying.
Great work today.
Great work.
- Great work. - Great work.
- Great work. - Gosh.
Grouchy 1 and 2.
(Preparing to eat)
Gosh, these plastic gloves...
are huge.
- They're in size large. - Yes.
They're large and fit well.
(The Giant Boy is happy about small things.)
- The gloves fit perfectly. - They do.
- Thank you. - Thank you. What a big feast.
What a generous feast.
- They all look fresh. - My gosh.
I love snow crabs.
For real, today...
- Yes, it's your first meal. - Since morning...
You saw it. This is my first meal.
Have some of this.
The abalone is delicious.
(My Star's precious meal)
It's good.
The food is fresh.
(Fasting restriction lifted)
Delicious.
With this?
- It's good. - It's really good.
You have to eat it warm for the best flavor.
It's really good.
You sure are digging in.
You look happy, Jang Hoon.
(I'm glad I brought you here.)
Today...
It's good.
I'm really being spoiled thanks to My Genie Secretary.
Totally.
I haven't had snow crabs in years, you know?
- Really? What a surprise. - For real?
- Seriously. - My gosh.
I only ever got deliveries.
What do you usually order?
You know just...
- Jjajangmyeon, - Oh, dear.
kimchi stew,
and sundae soup. It's one of those three.
- You're happy, right? - Yes.
(My Star is very happy today.)
Give me a bit more chojang.
(Taking care of the Young Master)
(Staring)
Kwang Kyu takes more care of...
Seo Jin than me.
That just now was a shocker.
(Taking care of the Young Master has become second nature.)
You see...
That just now was a shocker.
Watching Kwang Kyu fill up Seo Jin's chojang dish...
shocked me.
- Isn't today's My Star me? - It is.
He takes more care of Seo Jin than me.
Here's the commanding system.
When Jang Hoon gives me an order, I pass that on to Kwang Kyu.
That's the system.
It's how my life has always been.
(I should dig in to take care of Seo Jin.)
Kwang Kyu, you must love crabs.
- Of course. - It's really good eaten warm.
It's best when it's warm.
It's delicious.
(An advanced skill)
What's gotten into him?
(Munching)
- Me? - Are you in your andropause?
I'm in my andropause throughout the year.
(All year round)
I've been in my andropause since birth.
(Andropause symptoms: Decreased testosterone...)
(can increase appetite and lead to weight gain)
- I'm curious. - Are you not in your andropause?
Seo Jin is really cranky because it's hit him.
I'm not in my andropause yet.
It's just that...
I get a little sad at times since I've been single for so long.
That's andropause.
Are you lonely?
I'm not that lonely.
It's kind of different.
I'm not lonely because I don't have anyone by my side.
Exactly. That's andropause.
- That's andropause. - Really?
It's not because you're single.
Andropause has hit the two together.
I'm not lonely because I'm single.
Why am I...
- How much longer will I... - Anxiety and impatience...
- come rushing in. - Yes.
There's no reason behind it.
You become anxious and impatient for no reason.
- That's andropause. - What about this?
What about thoughts like, "Won't it get lonelier..."
"without anyone the more I grow older?"
That doesn't cross my mind.
Things like, "How nice would it be if someone greeted me at home?"
- No. - I love it...
when I enter my pitch dark house.
I don't like a lit up house.
He and I are on the same page on that.
(What the men have in common)
But the lights should be on.
I hate it when my house is dark.
When the lights are on, I'm like,
- "What?" - Don't you get anxious?
- Right? - Is it a thief?
"Did a thief break in?"
Say that I forgot to turn them off when I left.
"Oh, no. The electricity bills."
I'm fine with paying for a 1,000 dollar get-together meal.
Totally.
But it's a different story when it comes to using...
unnecessary energy at home.
The rich are worse.
(The frugal ones)
I recently splurged.
I changed my fridge.
- My kitchen is small. - I see.
I found this chicken fit.
- Kitchen fit? - Yes, kitchen fit.
Kwang Kyu just said chicken fit.
- Exactly. I thought I misheard him. - My bad.
I thought it was chicken feet when he said chicken fit.
- You mean your new house, right? - Yes.
Yes, I bought a kitchen fit.
The kitchen fit was more expensive than I imagined.
- How much was it? - It was a big decision.
It was around 3,200 dollars.
You didn't buy anything recently, did you?
(What's My Star's most recent purchase?)
- You don't buy things, do you? - Is it a building?
A building?
- A building is unbeatable. - No.
I can't remember what I bought.
(What did I buy again?)
Be honest about it.
But really, maybe he didn't buy anything.
- I bought squid. - Oh, my.
Did you buy a squid-catching boat?
From home shopping...
- Squid? - Why did you buy squid?
Half-dried!
I almost bought it.
I bought it.
You don't grill it at home, do you?
It said I didn't have to.
Exactly, we don't.
- Open it, and eat it as is. - I knew it.
Jang Hoon isn't the type to do things at home.
Okay, fine.
I bought squid, okay?
That's cute. Buying squid was cute.
Squid.
Jang Hoon, aren't you on many anger-inducing shows?
How do you usually keep yourself calm?
(How does My Star calm himself?)
You do an unusual number of...
- anger-inducing shows. - I do.
- You're on a dating show. - Yes.
- You're on a divorce-related show. - Yes.
- That's impressive. - Whenever...
I turn the TV on,
he's always frowning...
and sighing.
- This is him. - You can't see him smiling.
- He's like, "Sir." - Totally.
And then, he sets it up.
"Say, for example..."
Don't you get stressed out at home?
- Many do worry about me. - Right.
"Is he mentally okay..."
"after hearing all those stories?"
But my...
I want to show how sincere I am about the guests.
I'm nothing but genuine in those moments.
They're like...
my younger sister and brother,
older brother,
and older sister.
I give them sincere advice,
hoping they'll live happily.
But...
After the show...
On my way home...
- Do you get gift vouchers? - No.
(Cutting in)
(Financial therapy)
- I... - That's not impossible.
I forget about it...
on my way home after the show.
You do?
Yes, because I have more shows tomorrow.
If I don't forget about it,
it might affect...
(Forgetting about it quickly won't get in the way of other shows.)
the next show.
That's the mindset I have.
I shake it off quickly...
and prepare for the next show.
Earlier, I monitored...
- the show from start to finish. - I see.
The last question was,
"What does it mean to be truly rich?"
I heard the question was from you, Jang Hoon.
Correct.
What's the answer?
Who do you think is truly rich?
Like, what kind of a person.
(Who does My Star think is truly rich?)
For me,
it keeps changing as I grow old.
- Right now, at my age, - You're right.
someone who is truly rich...
has a big heart.
Someone with a big heart.
(My forehead is big.)
And someone easygoing. That's who is truly rich.
If someone is wealthy...
but narrow-minded?
From what I can see,
- they may... - Yes?
not become...
truly rich in the near future.
Someone with a big heart.
- That's a tough one. - Yes.
Who I think is a billionaire is...
- Yes? - Who is it?
someone who spends money freely on me.
What?
Someone who spends freely on me...
- A billionaire? - is a true billionaire.
Really?
Such a person...
won't be generous only with me.
They're someone who knows how to be generous to others.
Someone who spends a lot.
Those who spend freely on me are the truly rich.
Someone with a big heart...
who knows how to show kindness.
(Someone who shows kindness with their big heart)
Kwang Kyu, what kind of a person do you think is truly rich?
Seo Jang Hoon.
(An immediate answer)
That's a clear answer.
I love it.
(I love it.)
I had too much...
of a prejudice about Jang Hoon.
That fussiness you see on variety shows.
Complaining all the time.
Cussing and getting angry.
My assumptions about his expressions...
were shattered into a million pieces today.
Hanging out with him outside...
made me realize his childlike innocence.
Jang Hoon is an open-minded guy...
with a soft heart.
- In simple words. - Really,
today...
(How was it being taken care of today?)
Had it not been for the two guys,
the show...
might have been...
a little lonely midway.
But because the two guys I adore...
came...
all the way to Gangneung with me,
chatted...
with me,
and hung around with me,
I had a lot of fun.
I really appreciate it too.
If there's another chance,
I'd love to...
take care of those two.
I'm serious.
Anyway, that's how grateful I am.
- A warm thinker. - A warm thinker.
- Nice one. - Right?
(My Star is the warmest thinker.)
A warm-hearted thinker.
Do we welcome them?
Why is it different from the usual?
(My Stars CHOONGJU JI-C)
(Ji Ye Eun and Jee Seok Jin)
(The surprise guest CHOONGJU JI-C...)
(is at Chungju Music Festival!)
Are you rehearsing at K Karaoke?
(Raw live vocals hanging by a thread)
You're not good enough to stand on stage.
Even your moves aren't in sync.
(Outraged by the secretaries' brutal honesty)
(Even at the surprise CHOONGJU JI-C fan sign meeting)
(I want Lee Seo Jin's autograph.)
(Not ours?)
- You want Lee Seo Jin's? - Yes.
(I also want Lee Seo Jin's autograph.)
It's them today.
(The fans leave the fan sign meeting.)
(More complaints over the fan rivalry)
(Did you finally speak your mind?)
(No, he's scary.)
(My Star even pretended to be asleep.)
Seo Jin...
still wants to be the center of attention.
(My Star talks up a storm behind his back.)
(Just before the big performance)
People are packing up.
They don't know it's our turn.
(An unprecedented audience walkout?)
Please stop them.
Everyone left.
(Can My Stars finish the performance without a hitch?)
(My Genie Secretary)